<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Building My Life in the Margins</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Building My Life in the Margins</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2024, Eric Jones.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 20:46:14 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Test Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 20:46:14 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/test-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a page about »Test Post«.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Black Hole of Distractions and Configurations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/the-black-hole-of-distractions-and-configurations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 08:01:08 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/the-black-hole-of-distractions-and-configurations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I tend to find that if I’m presented with the opportunity to tinker and configure settings rather than just getting down to work, I can easily spend hours doing that and at the end of the day be annoyed that I didn’t actually doing anything productive. I’m now at that point in my “computing life” where I value a workspace that simply works and allows me to get to what actually matters rather than fiddling around endlessly trying to find that “perfect setup”.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airpods Pro 2 First Impressions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/airpods-pro-2-first-impressions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 07:55:20 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/airpods-pro-2-first-impressions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ve lived with the struggle of being overly sensitive to loud noises pretty much my entire life. Recently, I decided to pick up a pair of 2nd generation AirPod Pros. I was hesitant when placing the order, wondering if these were going to be worth the money, but let me tell you… these headphones are one of the best purchases that I’ve made in a long time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I can now walk to work on a busy weekend day and not have to have the anxiety of being overwhelmed with loud ambient noise. A quick press of the stem on the AirPods and the outside world fades out, allowing me to only focus on whatever music or podcast is playing. Surprisingly often, I just walk around with active noise cancellation enabled without any audio playing because having that silence is so wonderful.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/markdown-syntax-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href=&#34;https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&#34;&gt;https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/now/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;now&#34;&gt;Now&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This page is inspired by Derek Sivers’s post - &lt;a href=&#34;https://sive.rs/nowff&#34;&gt;/now page movement&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href=&#34;https://nownownow.com/about&#34;&gt;Now Movement&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The purpose of this page is to share what I’m currently focusing my energy towards (long and short term goals) and will update as things change.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-am-i-up-to-right-now&#34;&gt;What am I up to right now?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I’m currently pursuing a Bachelors of Science degree in Information Technology&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I’m currently employed at a Tech company working in Inventory Management&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I’m writing about various technical and personal topics&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I’m diving more headfirst into self hosted solutions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I’m starting to create more scripts to help automate repetitive tasks in my life (more blog posts on these to come)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-are-my-interests&#34;&gt;What are my interests?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Writing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Reading&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Photography&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;FOSS (Free Open Source Software)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Decentralization&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Automation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;GNU / Linux&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;which-operating-systems-do-i-use&#34;&gt;Which Operating Systems do I use?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;On the mobile side, I’m an iOS user&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;On the laptop/desktop side, I’m a macOS / Ubuntu Linux user&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;On the server side, I’m an Ubuntu Linux user&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;daily-drivers&#34;&gt;Daily Drivers&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;My phone is an iPhone 16 Pro Max&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;My laptop is a MacBook Pro 16” / Dell XPS 15”&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;My servers are a 2024 Mac Mini and Intel NUC&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This site is fueled by a human brain and lots of coffee. ☕️&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
